I think it's just for a week.
I'm in.
Is this it?
Yes, sir.
Yes!
Here we go.
Oh, TikTok Slime!
It's started.
Oh, it's started.
No, it's not coming.
It's done.
It's started.
It's definitely started.
This one.
I want to buy this.
Oh, my God.
Is this camera bad?
I want to buy this one.
Oh, here we go.
Is it on?
Yeah, the ads just started.
It's starting.
It's started.
Okay, I've started TikTok Live.
Oh, wow.
My first TikTok Live!
I'm going to do a lot of things on TikTok.
Maybe it's working.
Maybe I'm right.
I'll know.
Watch out for the feet.
Your feet.
A little more TikTok.
Here we go.
It's started.
Maybe we'll do TikTok too.
Oh, okay.
We're going to do a TikTok live.
So please come and watch us on either screen!
So, without further ado...
The next Bijo Cross last!
Inari Top Sanyan, please take care of her.
Thank you very much!
And now, it's time to announce the results of the Deliberate Mockery Championship!
Wow! It's started!
Thank you for waiting so long!
Let's see what it's all about.
Oh, yeah.
It's pretty much 100.
We're having a deliberate bruising championship.
out of all the people who have been hashtagged.
Each member picked their favorite and
We've decided on one grand prize winner.
I would like to have you announce it!
Please give your best wishes to the winners!
Okay, let's start with Kaya-chan.
Great!
What did the members choose?
Right.
I don't know.
Fun
I'm going to give you what you want.
I'm giving you all a present.
Yay!
What is Kaya's gift?
This is her trophy.
And, wow!
Kaya's present is
Here it is!
So cute! What's this?
This is the one
has wanted since she was a child.
You can learn by playing with it.
Click with the mouse
It's Anpanman Patocon!
Yay!
It's surprisingly expensive.
You wouldn't buy it by yourself, would you?
No, I didn't.
I bought it for him.
That's nice.
Okay, I'll put it in now.
What? I'm so happy.
It's on TikTokLive.
So, I can just put it in the thing?
You mean open it?
But, you know, if you keep the box...
You should write the box down.
The box.
Here we go.
Oh, that makes me happy.
I'm so happy.
It's so cool!
With Anpanman.
He said I can use it at work.
He said I can use it.
I want you to use it.
Cute!cute
pleasant to the touch
Cute hand-schooled
cute
5.27
Yes, ma'am.
This way, ladies and gentlemen.
There you are.
I'm so happy.
Okay, let's get to it.
Open it.
Look at that.
I'm so excited for you guys.
The TikTokLive people should see this.
I know, right?
Let's see.
Can I play it when you play it?
Yes, you can.
Volume maybe okay.
More pins?
Will it have volume?
It's going to be voluminous.
Just a little bit of volume.
Okay.
Oops.
Oh, no. Did we start?
I'll tell you something different.
I'll tell you something.
Yes, I'll teach you something different.
Let's give it up for Ayasho Datekawa.
Who will announce the results first?
Please announce the results.
Okay, then,
Let's announce the result!
Who is Ayasho Datekawa?
Ayasho Datekawa is..,
This way!
Who is it?
Up?
Front?
Back?
Isn't he cute?
It's a puppy!
Doggy, please play with this.
Oh, he's so cute!
So cute!
He's in the comments section of YouTube.
Really? They say it's delicious.
Oh, my! Congratulations!
What's your name?
Your name is Suzu.
Congratulations!
What's your point?
I love dogs,
You know, when he was my favorite dog,
I'm gonna put him in his cage.
It's like this.
It was so cute,
I was addicted to the sound,
I was really into the sound, so
I was so into the sound that I let her play it for me.
Congratulations!
A cute little dog.
What's going on? I'm serious.
It's amazing. It was pretty heavy.
I want this as an extra too.
I'll put it out next as an extra.
Mie-chan.
Next is Fujitani Mie winner.
The gift I chose is...
This and,
First, it's heavy.
The first one.
There were two,
The first one,
Can I tear it off?
Yes, you can. Open it.
We won't know if we don't open it.
I don't know who should open it.
I can see them, so I'll let them have it.
I'm opening it.
I'm sorry.
It makes a great noise.
It's rumbling.
It sounds weird.
Yes, it does.
The first one.
Here we go.
Jang.Jang.
Pizza socks.
Cute.
Can you see it?
What? It's so cute.
It's so cute.
It's cute.
How did you find it?
It's so cute.
It's really good.
I can see it so much.
It's cute.
This is cute.
Yes, and one more thing,
I missed it,
I don't know how to say this,
I have one of these at home.
It's personal.
It's in my room.
It's colorful.
You can't see it.
This is it.
It's gorgeous.
It's amazing.
Yes, it looks like this.
Cute.
A gift for the baby's baby.
Then announce.
I'll announce it!
I wonder what he chose.
Oh no, oh no, I chose the one called Boss.
Melia.
Here we go.
I hope I can make it.
Oh, my God, oh, my God, oh, my God.
Waiting?
He's so cute.
He's cute.
So cute.
I chose the baby.
I picked out a baby.
What's your name?
Mitsuhiro Sasaki.
Mitsuhiro?
He's cute.
He's cute. Please use it.
The point?
The point is, I can't dance. It's cute that she dances all the time like this.
Also, she took 3 pictures on this account.
He also made an account for this Masa and Asaku.
I see.
I chose it because I wanted it for a long time.
Please use it.
Thank you very much.
Next, Mon-chan.
Yes, ma'am.
First of all, the profiles are here.
It's bad over here, too.
The pick check is pretty bad.
This way.
Do you see it?
I see it.
It's bad over here, too.
Present.
That's what I'm talking about.
So, what is it? What? What?
The present is here.
What?
This way, this way.
So cute!
Doraemon's light that glows when you tap it.
So cute.
Please put your hand in bed with me.
I want this one Yuna.
I want it.
Cute.
It's adorable.
Who can have this one?
Oh!
Who's there?
Who's there? Who's there?
Doraemon's in the mirror.
What does he want?
It's coming.
Right this way, sir.
Wow!
It's Riko!
That's Riko!
She's so cute!
So cute!
She's so cute.
Amazing!
Amazing.
It's so cute.So cute!
That's amazing.
That's great.
Yes, ma'am.
Thank you very much.
She's so cute.
She did a lot of illustrations and editing for me.
You know, elaborate things.
You put a lot of time and effort into it.
You took the time to make it for me.
I could feel the love he had for me.
so I chose him for this contest.
I chose this one.
Akamachi
Now, let's see what you've got back there.
Congratulations!
Can you tell by the way you hit it?
That's great.
I just finished my shift.
I'm working now.
I wonder if it's going up.
I'm taking a break.
I see.
Akari's cute.
Only Fine?
Oh, Shizuke.
I'm really happy that you use Fine too.
I'm so happy!
I feel love.
If you don't love it, you can't make it.
I can't make it
Hey.
Because I'm already thinking
Love.
Love is amazing.
Mai's power is infinite
Mai makes the earth
Cherry blossoms
The Moon
The night sky
We can connect there
Lovely.
Cute.
Good editing.
Looks good.
Oh, they're making it.
That's the one, right? Um..,
Fuku Koi?
Yes, yes, yes.
That's right.
Ah.
That was amazing.
I worked hard.
Thank you.
Congratulations.
Here they come.
Good night face.
Congratulations.
Thank you.
Okay, Karen, you're up next.
Okay, Karen.
Ms. Cullen.
Okay. Now, I would like to present the Karen Tachibana Award.
Oh.
What?
Karen's choice.
You have a present for me.
I chose it.
Oh, here it is.
Here.
What? What?
Well then...
It's a MOBUSOBA catsuit.
Eeeee...
It's cute.
So cute.
This is a queen kanpuru,
It's in a catsuit,
When you eat it, the buckwheat drops down from here.
Cute.
It's cute.
It sure looks expensive.
So, by all means, please try this.
It's so delicious.
Yes, it is.
So if you wear it, I'll give you a receipt thinking that I want it.
I want you to wear it.
It's amazing.
No, it's not like this.
It's super cute.
It's cute.It's pretty, isn't it?
Yes, it is. It's like that.
It's cute.
It's delicious.
It's amazing.
He's impressed.
Look at that with your dad.
Is that okay?
Yes, I'm sure.
I'm so happy for you.
Why don't you answer it?
I've been watching a lot of stuff.
I decided to go with the one that made me giggle.
It's very twisted.
Is there any way to turn that off?
Isn't that good?
No, it's not.
Is there any way to turn it off?
It works. It works. It works. It works.
Thank you very much.
I'm so happy.
Ms. Karin Tachibana.
Yes, thank you very much. Thank you very much.
Yes, this is Ms. Karin Tachibana, whom I have chosen.
sindra
as
Teita
ai
me
This is Mr. Koji. Congratulations!
This is Koji, who was dancing in a very small place in a very small rice paddy,
I thought it was interesting, and I also thought it was very impressive,
The last one.
I thought it was the last one, so I chose it.
I would be very happy if you could put it on.
Thank you very much.
Oh, on the back.
Just put it on, okay?
Try it on.
Thank you very much.
Thank you so much.
Yum! Yum!
It's great.
Can I put this on for the first time?
Oh, really?
Oh, good.
I'm in a real hurry now.
I'd probably laugh if I saw it.
You'd laugh at me.
You'll put it on.
He's my favorite pineapple.
He's on Wi-Fi and everything.
That's for sure.
Then let's go to the kitchen and decide.
What the hell?
Here's the present I chose.
It's a full-on slam dunk.
There's a lot of them!
Now you and I are slam dunk friends!
So the happy bag I chose is...
What other readings?
I want to read Yu's too!
Seino
Lance
Lance.
That's great.
The main guy who writes for us.
This guy
This is Manmaruko.
Thank you.
The points I chose are
I like comic books.
It's like
like a cartoon character.
Thank you very much.
Congratulations!
Thank you so much.
And the others.
I've seen a lot of them.
Thank you so much.
Good.
Congratulations!
congratulations
I feel like a teacher.
Is this a national duo?
Oh, my God.
My favorite time of the day.
You should do your favorite time.
I'm so glad.
Thank you so much!
Let's go here once.
It's the first time since I've been here.
The fastest.
It's definitely 13 minutes.
If it was around there
A little bit.Just a little.
It's a rainy day.
Take a break, okashi-oha.
Bye, bye, bye.
What's going on?
What's up?
Hey...
I don't want to go anywhere!
This is it.
You didn't open it?
What?
What's that?
Is it a proposal?
Proposal?
Oh, no, no, no, no, no.
Oh, no, no, no, no.
Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Dah dah dah dah dah dah dah dah dah dah dah dah dah dah dah dah dah dah dah dah dah dah.
Dekar.
Yes, I'm giving you a gift.
Diesel bracelet!
Wow!
Wait a minute.
I want one more, so you put it on once.
Wow, it's so cute!
So cute!
The design is
Cute
Cute.
I like it. It's diesel.
I know.
It's so cute.
I thought it was super cute and chose it.
Stylish!
I like this one too.
I boarded the plane myself, and I thought I'd transport it myself.
I see.
Yes, I've chosen him.
That's what I was thinking.
Oh, Lisa.
Hey, hey, Memi.
O-tomori's
T-shirt Mon fleek
Oh, yes, yes, yes.
She looks so happy to open it.
So cute.
It's cute.
Cute.
It looks so lived-in.
It's cute.
It's warm.
I chose MEGGI.
Congratulations.
Thank you.
What I thought was nice was that you went to the trouble of setting up the camera, even though you were supposed to be on your way home from work,
I thought it was interesting that you took the trouble to set up the camera and made it look like you were peeking in, and I chose it because I thought you were living a proper life at home.
Thank you.
Thanks for all the other submissions.
I like it.
That means you've been out of the house even once, right?
That's right.
That means you've been away from home.
Cute.
He's cute.
He's so cute.
I saw the T-shirt once.
No, it's not.
It's not.
No, no, no.
No, it's not.
It's,
Yumeshima's crying routine.
Crying routine.
Oh, yeah.
That's adorable.
So cute.
It's falling.
Indeed.
Cute.
It's cute.
On the face.
I noticed you've gone.
I'm glad.
If I see it here.
I see.
Maybe.
I'll go sign it.
And if you have any other comments...And if you have any more comments.
Cute.
Comments are good.
This is a letter.
A certain ys of rebirth
You talk about palate like this?
I don't have much trouble with a small salary.
It's been a while.
What is this?
What is it?
I'm so happy.
I wish you'd make some of this stuff.
Let's make it into a comic book!
What?
Who's going to write it?
We're looking for artists.
We're looking for an artist!
Let's make it look like the author.
Yoo-hoo!
I love it!
I hope you read a lot.
I'd love to read it.
Next to the middle of the page.
Be my guest.
I'm happy... on both sides.
I'm happy for you.
Happy project
As a total picture of what we've done so far
If you notice...
Me?
Let's see...
Overall flow
Tendency of the destination
Selected Destination Trends
It's still each individual's
What sticks with each individual
It depends on the person
What sticks with each person
After all
It changes.
A little upset
A little upset.
I have a few of them.
I'll give them to you right away.
That's great.
It's a little bit amazing, the things that stick out, each one of them.
I'm sure we'll find out in the future what they like.
Yes, it's a great way to get to know each other.
It also helps us to know what we want now.
Yes, that's true.
I really want it.
I want it, we all want it.
I want MIRUSITA
I want MIRUSITA! I want MIRUSITA!
I want you all. I want you all.
Okay, let's start with Yumeran.
I want Dorodoro.
I want Minna-chan.
I want you.
Give it back.
Give me back!
Give it back!
Yes, that's it.
Next, we have the HATSUKI-UNAWA show!
Hazuki Una
Hazuki unagi
What is it?
The place where it opens
The part that opens
I wonder what's in the opening part
But if I tell you who it is, you'll already know.
Don't you get it, guys?
I'm 100% sure it's not open.
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
I know.
But how do we open it?
I just need to put this back on the ribbon.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
It's okay.
Still more.
Even more.
Oh, my God.
It's sturdy.
It's like Yuna.
Yeah, that's the kind of Yuna I want.
Oh, no, this is going to rip.
I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
Oh, no, I'm sorry.
Oh, I'll have to open this one even more.
Oh, wait!
Oh, wait, what is it?
I'm in a box, in a box, in a box.
Should I open this one, too?
Should I show you what's inside?
It's kind of like a rip-off box.It's like a box of rips.
It's not like I'm going to open the box.
I don't think it's blue.
Uh, rips.
Oh, I don't know.
But it's a little bit like...
It's a little bit like that.
Not? A little bit like him?
Maybe a little bit like Asayuru.
You look a little bit like him.
Oh, God.
Can we not do this anymore? I'm sorry.
Sorry.
More and more boxes.
Oh, here it is. Here it is.
Well, here's what I'm giving you.
It's a Liptik colored candle.
Wow!
It's real!
It's really nice.
Yuna, I really like this.
It smells so good! I want some!
It's 300g, and I have the 50g one.
And it's a colored candle.
It's really pure white and transparent.
So I'd love to have this one.
Suddenly I'm sniffing Bun-nu.
I'm doing the Bun nu.
It's a very noticeable smell.
But when I looked up what it smelled like...
All it says is "B".
BB.
What's good about it, it doesn't have a B scent.
I don't know.
I wonder what it smells like.
I recommend this place.
I don't know, I think it's called "B" or something like that.
Scent B.
I see what you mean.
Okay, so...
I chose this fashionable one.
Here's the type I chose for the supposedly Yuna show
BB
No, really, you know, I've done this many times.
This is still not the one you laugh at.
I chose the one that beats this drama.
Are you seeing this?
It's amazing.
That's great.
Congratulations. Tanya.
It's really great that you're hitting the drama,
I was doing some kind of head-bang thing at the beginning.
He said that was my jar.
I'm laughing my whole life.
But I'm really sorry that I was probably taking it so seriously.
It's okay.
And I probably wouldn't use these candles.
For sure.
So I thought maybe I should pick a girl or something,
But I decided to be fair about it,
So I decided to be fair about it, and I chose the person who wore pink,
I hope that Tanya will be able to get stuck into the candles with this picture.
Then, what about Takinae?
And then he made me say "headbang" even more.
Well then, congratulations.
Yes, but that's all.
I'm going to give you a gift that's already difficult to give on its own.
Interesting.
Now, I would like to announce the first prize for everyone.
The product I chose is,
Ta-da!
A 38mm Kootenay!
Can it cut hair?
I want it.
I chose a very good one,
I hope you will use it.
I want it in general.
Let's go.
Here is the one I chose.
What a girl.
Cute.
Oh, you see?
This type is cute.
There is a point I chose this one,
I had 5 hashtags with the name Kitamirine,
I felt my love for her,
I also felt my love for her because she was wearing a catsuit and I really felt my love for her,
So I chose her as an expert.
It's nice.
Cute.
Rumble, rattle, rattle.
It's true.
And it's a girl.
Indeed.
It's useful.
It's Kazachan. And her hair is really curly.
I thought it would be useful.
It's cute and useful.
Do you want to touch it?
It's fine.That's fine.
I'm curious.
Like a touch lens.
It's amazing.
Hina has one too.
It's nice. People with long hair look so cute with it.
Yoshimori is really good with this,
I bought it after Yoshimori did my makeup with it.
I see.
And it's really easy to curl.
Mai-chan is here to play.
It comes with a rest.
This is really easy to use.
Really?
It's so easy to use.
It's really up-grounded.
It's really great.
Two more things.
I'm curious.
I'm excited.
I can tell I'm having too much fun.
Fashionable.
The point?
The point I chose?
The point I chose,
I like to watch you edit and stuff,
I also like to see other Mel-chan's edits,
I was very happy to see that you did it yourself,
It was cute and I went with it.
That girl put a lot of other stuff on there, so,
I was so happy to see so many kids there that I chose her.
Surprise! I'm so happy! Yes!
What do you think?
How about a trophy expression?
Yes, this is Mikila.
Mikira has a unit of units.
Mikira has a unit of the unit.
Let's see, here are the gifts.
Two colors.
I wonder what they are.
The first one is,
What's this?
What? What is it?
It's cute.
Ta-da!
This is..,
Oh, my God.
That's amazing. I'm so happy.
This is..,
I have this, and this is a sweatshirt,
This is a sweatshirt, but this is something else,
T-shirt? And this one is a T-shirt,
And here,
Embroidery,
It's an artist's brand,
You can embroider any word you like
of your favorite word,
I chose Run-chan,
and embroidered it.
It's amazing.
They have matching designs.
I'm so happy.
Here it is.
What is it?
Oh, my.
I'll open it.
The bag is cute.
I really wanted this,
I'm a little frustrated.
I don't know.
It was really hard to choose.
I really wanted it.
I wanted to give it to you.
Because I want it myself.
I want to give it to you.
Here we go.
Ta-da!
He's so cute.
Poor little thing.
What is it?
Cute.
cute
It's a white rabbit instance set!
wow!
I really wanted this.
That something to carry around and take pictures with your food,
Think of this as Rune-chan and go out together.
Cute.
Yes, it's Runchan.
It's Run-chan.
Okay, then,
It's cute.
I chose this one,
This way.
This is the sink that kept refilling the one who is being refilled. Please make friends with them.
Thank you.
Best regards.
Best regards.Best regards.
I am smiling while looking at Kari.
Cute.
I am smiling.
By the two of you taking pictures,
They named her "Ikebokuro".
Thank you.
He's smiling, isn't he?
It's so cute that you're wearing it.
I named it Nico Nico Nico,
I named him Nico Nico Nico,
I named him "Ikebokuro".
Cute.
Madoka.
Congratulations.
Cute.
So cute!
The editing is intentional.
She's going to change her name.
I'm glad you did that.
What are the points you chose?
The point I chose. Oh, you said it.
I did.
It's nice.
It has character.
Yes, it does. It's individuality.
Not at all, not at all.
I don't know how many methods there were this time.
There were quite a few.
I scrolled through so many.
There are so many more to choose from.
There are so many.
Should I go pull them together into a present?
Is it really for my own convenience?
Or just go for the cute ones?
Or do I choose as many kinds as I want?
There are so many things to choose from,
It was really difficult.
Thank you so much for your wonderful contribution.
Thank you very much.
Yes, it's true.
You know, people are not used to TikTok,
I hope you all are doing your best on TikTok, which you are not used to,
And they started using this as an opportunity to start their own TikTok,
And also..,
And also, fans are taking pictures of each other,
Yes, that's right.
And then there's the Grand Prix.
Oh, I see. There is still the Grand Prix.
There is still the Grand Prix.
Yes, there is.
Is the Grand Prix the best one?
Well, yes, of course.
I'd like to give this one the grand prize.
What do you get for the grand prize?
That.
What?
What is that?
A grand prize?
The grand prize,
There will be a Grand Prix.
The tiny grand prix.
Yes, a tiny one.
I'm in.
What?
What? Are you serious?
What? We're both going.
What happened to the Grand Prix?
The Grand Prix,
That's so funny.
But I think I want that one the most.
Isn't it rare?
It's rare.
I really want to see it.
What? Can I write about it?
If I do, I'll write it later.
What?
I want to.
This is so funny.
Ha-ha-ha-ha.
Do you want to show it to everyone?
After you.
Oh, you mean like that?
I thought this was Sunball.
Ha-ha-ha.
Oh, my God.
What? Why? Why?
Let's go in the back.
Come on, come on!
Wait!
Something here, too.
What's that?
What? Why? Why? Why?
Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
You sure?
Okay, I'll introduce you one more time.
You're okay with that?
Of course it's okay.That's right.
Okay, first of all, the Grand Prize winner.
I'd like to invite you to join us.
No, no, no.
And from a few minutes ago, everyone...
What's that?
Is it the grand prize product that you've been saying?
Yes, that's right.
Here's the product.
Ta-da!
What is it?
A safe.
It's a safe.
Can I show you the whole front page?
Do you want me to show you where to start?
Do you have a preference?
I'm not that particular.
It's kind of normal, isn't it?
What's that back there?
What is this?
I don't know why this is on the wall.
And who is this?
Lun-chan is here, too.
That's Lung-chan.
I smell it.
Like wrestling.
Oh, my God, the last one.
The ceiling is signed by Cappen.
I've never seen that before, but it's Cappen's autograph.
That's nice.
That's a rarity.
I see what you mean.
Your signature's changed.
My signature.
I have it.
That's great.
You can sign this.
Cappen's autograph.
I want it.
I think there's some money inside.
I'm sure.
What? I want some money. I want some money.
What? You're gonna give me this number?
What? What's in it? They're all like, "What's in it?
You know, you should definitely put something in there,
Captain.
I'll be happy to put something in it for you later, like your favorite candy or something.
Don't give me a number.
Oh, I know what it is.
I'm glad.
It's funny.
It's funny, isn't it?
Please introduce me.
It won't open?
Oh, but, you see, there's a hole right here.
It's in your camera.
Don't be afraid.
Well, then.
Oh, here.
You chose this one?
Do you know what you're doing?
I know what I'm talking about.
Now, I would like to introduce the Grand Prize.
This year's Deliberate and Intentional Championship,
The Grand Prize,
Oh!
In case you didn't know it was all high ili after being told so many times.
What a big high risotto!
Plastic beat속
IrishGalaxy solo
barber
Korejie buck
It's a wonder!
So, to all the participants in the TikTok world,
Kawachi Tsuchizaka.
Thank you very much.
This is also something, only Yuna followed me.
Yes. It was fun.
He was lucky.
So congratulations.
You posted a lot, didn't you?
Yes, about 500.
That's right.
It was also a hot topic during the tour.
You gave us 7 pieces each.
I love it.
He said it came from that side.
Seven at a time.
Seven each.
That was fun. Thank you very much.
Thank you very much.
Fun, something.
Yes, it was. It was fun.
I got to know everyone's personality.
I was happy.
Everyone danced in so many different ways.
I want you to dance a lot.
I had a lot of fun.
Thank you very much.Thank you.
Thank you.
Yes, thanks to all of you.
Thank you very much.
It's been fun. And the other people who are not in demand.
Demand?
There is demand.
So, the rest of you, too,
Please take a look at all of them.
I'm trying to be nice.
That's a nice word.
Really.
If you're one of the winners, please DM me and let me know where you live.
Please let me know your address or something.
I'll go to the group's DM.
Well then, congratulations.
Thank you.
It would be nice if we could do something like this again.
Yes, it would be. I'd like to do it.
The reason why you made the expert on purpose this time was also to have him do it on TikTok.
I wanted to have it on TikTok.
We were lucky enough to have a lot of people use it, and it was the first time for us to do a project like this.
It was the first time for us to do this kind of project.
It was a lot of fun, wasn't it?
Yes, it was. Everyone got so excited.
But, you know, I'm still an expert on purpose, on purpose.
That's right.
This year, we're going to go to Tohoku on purpose, on purpose, on purpose.
We want to get an award from TikTok, too.
Ah.
Like the TikTok Awards.
We're going to be in Tohoku on purpose, on purpose.
That sounds dangerous.
It's not that bad.
I'm just trying to get to that level.
That's for sure.
Then there might be a second round.
Yes, that's right.
Then we might get another award.
Please do.
If we break even together.
Yes, that's right.
I'll keep pushing for the whole year.
That's right.
I will keep pushing.
I think you see a cute Tohoku-san.
Indeed.
I'll be happy if you come out next time.
See you soon!
I will go at once.
Thank you very much.
Hey, I'm glad.
It's flowing.
Yes! It's flowing.
It's flowing. I'm happy.
Hey, by all means, I'd like to continue
I'd love to do it on purpose.
Please do.
So, today, we are going to announce the results of the
delivery of the results of the deliberate bruising championship.
Thank you very much!
Well then!
That's all! Jiro! That's all for the start story!
The talk started suddenly! Thank you very much!
Thank you!
Congratulations!